tuxpi.com 2016-08-04

# Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. 

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.tuxpi.com and how it is used. 

## Uploaded Files

All files you upload to tuxpi.com are deleted from our server after a short timespan, normally after 2-3 hours. 

## Sharing Photos

This website does not provide any hosting of photos itself but allows you to send images to third party sites for storage. Image hosting is currently provided by imgur.com. You can find their TOS and privacy policy [here](http://imgur.com/tos). 

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.tuxpi.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. 

We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order to remember the last photo you did upload. This way you can use another photo effect without having to upload the image again. A session ID cookie normally expires when you close your browser or after around two hours. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense / DoubleClick, Adbrite. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.tuxpi.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

In addition, DoubleClick may serve ads on this and other websites using the DART ad-serving technology. In doing so, the ad servers will place or read a unique ad-serving cookie on your computer and will use non-personal information about your browser and your activity at this site to serve ads on this and other sites. The ad-serving cookie is a persistent cookie. Please [click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/dart_adserving.asp) for more information about DoubleClick ad serving or to opt-out of the DoubleClick ad-serving cookie. 

www.tuxpi.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.tuxpi.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
